culturemap.com 2010-12-15

# Privacy Policy - CultureMap Houston

We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. The policies below are applicable to the culturemap.com website ("Website") produced and maintained by Culture Map LLC (collectively "Company" or "we", "us", or "our"). We have established this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather during your visit to the Website, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, and how you can manage your personal information.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered online at our website. It does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline, or to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link.

**By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Website and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this Privacy Policy retroactively, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or don't see your concerns addressed here, you should contact us by email at info@culturemap.com

**What Information About Me Is Collected and Stored?**

Culture Map adheres to the highest standards of ethical practices in all of our operations and is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our Website. **Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we don't sell, barter, give away, or rent your personal information to any company outside of Culture Map.** For purposes of registration, we may collect identifiable information about you such as your name, email address, and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code. We also may collect your browser type, domain name, access times and referring websites addresses.

**Personal Information**

So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced experience, we request that you register for a personal account accessible through a confidential password and nickname that you select. For purposes of registration, we only collect or may in the future collect identifiable information about you such as your nickname, email address, and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code. We also collect and store information that you enter into this Website, if applicable, or that you provide through our help desk, customer service representatives, or requests for more information. Registration may also be required and Personal Information may also be collected in certain portions of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g. community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards). We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database.

**Anonymous Information**

In addition, when you interact with the Website, our servers may keep an activity log that does not identify you individually ("Anonymous Information"). Generally, this information is collected though "traffic data". We collect and store certain administrative and traffic information including: source IP address, time of access, date of access, web page(s), software crash reports and type of browser used.

**Use of Cookies and Spyware**

We never use or install spyware on your computer, nor do we use spyware to retrieve information from your computer.

Also, like many Websites, we use "cookies", which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages that record your preferences. We use cookies to track use of the Culture Map service. We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve the Website and make it easier and/or relevant for your use. You may occasionally get cookies from companies advertising on our behalf. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to this cookie policy.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Like some Websites, we may use web beacons. A web beacon is an invisible graphic on a web page that is programmed to collect non-personally identifiable information about your use of a given website. Like cookies, web beacons allow Culture Map and its technology providers to summarize overall usage patterns for our analysis and provide personalized services. We do not share or provide personally identifiable information we may collect through such web beacons, such as names, e-mail addresses and phone numbers with our advertisers without your express permission.

We work with third-party advertising companies who may utilize cookies or web beacons to better provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These partners do not have access to or use your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information; they may, however, anonymously track your Internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond this Website.

**Is Information Collected From Children?**

This is not a Website directed to children under the age of 13, and Culture Map does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use this Website, and under no circumstance should you send information about yourself to Culture Map. If Culture Map discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided Culture Map with personal identifiable information, Culture Map will immediately delete that child's information from the Website.

**How We Use Your Information?**

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our Website or your Personal Information collected online to any companies not affiliated with us.

**Customer Service and Feedback**

We may use your Personal Information to fulfill orders, provide customer service, track your compliance with the Website's rules and regulations, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when you provide the information). In the event we plan to publicly post any of your Personal Information on a Website (as, for instance, a letter), you are provided prior notification of such posting and given the option of preventing such posting.

**Use of Anonymous Information**

We use Anonymous Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our users are so we can improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible. We also use Anonymous Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use Website. We may also use or share Anonymous Information (or other information, other than Personal Information) in any other manner that we deem appropriate or necessary.

**Third-party Agents**

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, fraud protection, etc. These entities have access to the Personal Information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that Personal Information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Website.

**Transactional partners**

We may share non-personal information with our partners and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Website during a specific time period. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.

**Emergency Situations**

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) protect and defend the our rights or property, the Website or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

**What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?**

The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Personal Information collected by our Website is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public.

While we try our best to safeguard your Personal Information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**What Happens When I Link To or From Another Web Site?**

This Website may contain links to other websites operated by affiliates of Culture Map or third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy for Culture Map do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. These other sites may also send their own cookies to you, collect your data or solicit your Personal Information. Always be aware of where you end up. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other Websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Website and read the privacy policies of each and every Website that you visit.

**What About Contests and Sweepstakes?**

If/when we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to this Website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed, if it is different than as described in this Privacy Policy. Personal Information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

**Public Areas, Chat Rooms and Newsgroups**

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards or feedback sections, becomes public, and therefore this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any Personal Information that you expect to keep private.

**Governing Law/Assignment**

The Website is published in the United States. We make every effort to protect the personal identifiable information of all users the Website. We attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws to the extent they may apply to the Culture Map services. If you are uncertain whether this privacy policy conflicts with the applicable local privacy laws where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to Culture Map. If you are located within the European Union, you should be aware that your personal identifiable information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by the European Union to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

We may change its ownership or corporate organization while providing the Website and services. As a result, please be aware that we may transfer your information to another Company that is affiliated with us or with which we have merged. Under such circumstances Culture Map would to the extent possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

**Changes to This Policy**

We are committed to maintaining its position as a premier Website on the Internet. As our Website continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Website. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use our website in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.

**Opt-Out and Correction Procedures**

You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters from Culture Map. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about you. We also permit you to correct or update Personal Information that you have previously provided to us. To do so, you can send us a message at info@culturemap.com.  
**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Culture Map who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to info@culturemap.com.
